Guide to the Leo K. Bustad Papers 1912-2005
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 5: Audiovisual Materials
  - Subseries 5.4: Audiocassettes
    - Dr. Mary Foster (New Zealand) "Chickens-Environmental Preference" Reverence for Life, 1981 May 18 (Folder 44)
    - Animal rights, undated (Folder 44)
    - Men and Molecules: the unique American Chemical Society radio series: coal's new face Dr. Bernard Lee and more power, less pollution Dr. D. Bienstock, undated (Folder 44)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 44)
    - B. Rollin PPP-stress and euthanasia, undated (Folder 44)
    - Side A small cirtters Side B choosing a pet, undated (Folder 44)
    - Dr. Bonnie Beaver puppy selection and Dr. Ian Dunbar psychological method of dog training, 1981 May 14 (Folder 44)
    - Hunger symposium, 1981 April 24 (Folder 44)
    - Side 1 Reverence for Life grief 1986 January 29 Side 2 commitment and service to nature, 1986 January 30 (Folder 44)
    - PPP program, undated (Folder 44)
    - F. Tomson, 1986 September 18 (Folder 44)
    - E.T. York, 1980 October 28 (Folder 44)
    - Side 1 choosing a pet - Ruth Side 2 choosing a pet - Dave, undated (Folder 44)
    - 3, undated (Folder 44)
    - Side 1 environmental ethics, grief Side 2 endangered species II, undated (Folder 44)
    - Ethics copy, undated (Folder 44)
    - 1st side - Reverence for Life - Pettinger 2nd side same, undated (Folder 44)
    - Wildlife diseases, 1983 March 02 (Folder 44)
    - Copy of Amelie Pettinger's goal, undated (Folder 44)
    - Tape 2 side 1 Dr. McCulloch movie "Just a Little Hope", undated (Folder 44)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 45)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 45)
    - Roger Fouts, undated (Folder 45)
    - Dr. Ian Dunbar "Prevention and Treatment of Behavioral Problems in Dogs", 1981 May 14 (Folder 45)
    - Latham Foundation symposium speakers, WSU ("hard to hear"), 1980 March (Folder 45)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 45)
    - Phil Arkow program design, undated (Folder 45)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 45)
    - Pet therapy tv interviews in Ohio, undated (Folder 45)
    - Bill Terner, undated (Folder 45)
    - "Lord, did you see me wave?" Leo Bustad LITE, 1986 July (Folder 45)
    - Reverence for Life, undated (Folder 45)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 45)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 45)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 45)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 45)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 45)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 45)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 45)
    - Guidelines: animals in institutions, undated (Folder 45)
    - Missa Gaia-Paul Winter, undated (Folder 45)
    - Do animals think?, undated (Folder 45)
    - LKB's history, undated (Folder 45)
    - Concert of Latin-American music Bill Dexheimer and friends, 1989 August 08 (Folder 45)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 45)
    - Animals in entertainment Dr. White, circa 1980 (Folder 45)
    - Trinity Lutheran Church 9:00 service, 1989 September 27 (Folder 45)
    - Grief and loss circa, 1990 (Folder 45)
    - Nursing home slides script/PPP, undated (Folder 45)
    - Therapeutic horseback riding III/stable management games/backriding (cont.) IV Beth Stanford, LPT, 1986 November 15 (Folder 45)
    - Mary Futrell, 1980 November 11 (Folder 45)
    - Bruce Tetus Conue, 1982 January 22 (Folder 45)
    - People pet, undated (Folder 45)
    - Delta M.McC, undated (Folder 45)
    - Tape 3, undated (Folder 45)
    - Humaneness and compassion LK Bustad Reverence for Life, 1985 November (Folder 45)
    - People-pet course, undated (Folder 46)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 46)
    - Talk on humaneness, etc to 1st year students, 1979 November (Folder 46)
    - The Finn Who Wouldn't Take a Sauna, undated (Folder 46)
    - PPP March 13, undated (Folder 46)
    - Non-pet, undated (Folder 46)
    - Responsibilities of pet ownership, undated (Folder 46)
    - Conversation with counsel Titus, 1982 January 04 (Folder 46)
    - Dr. Hodgson ethics case, undated (Folder 46)
    - Deposition tape one, undated (Folder 46)
    - Deposition tape two, undated (Folder 46)